All pirates searching for the treasure of One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best in Marineford. Luffy and his crew reunite to continue on to the New World.
The first stop on their journey is Fishman Island, which resides thousands of feet below sea level.
Now, they're separated once again, stirring up trouble all over the ocean floor.
Luffy smuggled the Princess Shirahoshi out of Ryugu Palace for an adventure.
Robin received a lead on the whereabouts of a pony glyph hidden on Fishman Island.
The crew can take care of themselves. I can't miss a chance to uncover the world's lost history.
Frankie stumbled upon the sunny at the sea forest, a resting place for sunken ships.
I'll do the ship coding for you. And I'll do it with gusto.
Hmm. Haven't heard that one in a while. Oh, uh, sorry. I never caught your name.
Call me Den.
By the way, I've been meaning to ask you. There's a dude sitting all alone over there. Do you know who he is?
Uh-huh. That would be the boss, Jinbei. Consider it a term of endearment. He's waiting for someone.
After Zoro, Usopp, Nami, and Brook managed to accidentally seize the palace,
they found themselves face to face with the rebel uprising of Hordi and Vanderdecken, who were out to destroy Ryugu Kingdom.
Someone took my Shira Hoshi? This is a tragedy!
She's not yours. And damn right it's a tragedy.
We've been in love for ten years. Nothing can tear us apart, princess.
Except death, that is.
If I can't have you, then nobody can.
You're about to be a big beautiful corpse, Shira Hoshi!
The Battle in the Ryugu Palace. Zoro versus Hordi.
Oh, that one's an octopus. And that looks like a blowfish. And look, there's a keely fish over there.
That's lame. Do all clouds look like fish to you?
That's a rice ball! And that one looks like a giant donut!
A chunk of meat!
They all look like food to you, Luffy.
Guess so!
No!
Ja-mung! Ja-mung! Ja-mung!
Hold on. What's the matter with you now?
My poor father. He surely found me missing. He must be worried sick by now.
Ah, jeez. Is there anything that doesn't make you cry?
Oh, my!
Cheer up, you sissy!
You goof!
Hey, I'm not trying to make you laugh! Small, we're back up, shark!
Ah!
Flander Deccan is going to capture my precious Shira Hoshi!
Oh, Neptune!
Please, I beg of you people. I'll give you anything you ask for.
Just let me go after Deccan.
You can have my kingdom's fortune! You can even take my soldiers' lives if you want!
No king! They can't!
I can't let that beast catch Shira Hoshi!
My Sweden is a not-so-little girl!
You're quite the pathetic sight, Neptune.
But what a shock.
I was confident that I could take the palace.
But I never thought the loathsome straw hats would be part of the story.
He knows us?
He's got the mark of Arlong on his arm.
Heheheheheheh!
Jingbei! He tried to warn me that there was something wicked going on in the Fishman district.
But you! How could a former soldier of Neptune's Army be the ringleader?
Shame on you! Hordy!
Heheheh! Shame, huh?
I'm sorry. I can't drum up any shame, maybe because I never felt pride in the army to begin with.
Listen, there's only one reason why I joined, and that was to learn combat skills so I could turn this world upside down. Simple as that.
You traitor. You helped me set things right.
What do you mean?
The comforts of your royal palace have blinded you to what's been happening on this island.
Ever since I was a child, as far back as I can remember, I've seen fishmen oppressed by barbaric humans.
Help me, someone!
All the trouble it took to get to this island. We might as well grab a couple of souvenirs to take back with us, huh?
Please just let me go! Help!
Give us back a friend!
Well, look at this. A couple of rowdy fishman brats. You want to join us?
I mean, you're not worth as much as any merfolk. But you know, if we sell you off as a set, the auction house might cut us a deal.
All right. I've heard enough of your crap.
Pathetic creatures can't even breathe underwater. And yet, no matter how many we kill, they don't stop.
Orlong had a fierce determination to suffocate the arrogance out of humankind. I deeply admired him for that.
And now, we will restore his dream. The new fishman pirates continue his legacy!
Huh?
He was the reason I cultivated my strength. I had to train until I was strong enough to become Orlong's right-hand man.
I dreamed of standing by his side when he conquered the world from the East Blue.
Well, I did. Until you humans came along and crushed everything he worked for.
Oh, man. I thought we were done with Orlong. Can't you just let it go?
What? Not Orlong?
I'm just kidding.
In truth, I don't even know who Orlong is. I just didn't want to be left out, you know?
How rude! I'll have you know that I bruise easily!
Shut up. This is no time for jokes!
Enough chit-chat. We have business. So let's get down to it.
Stand back!
What the...?
Shark grip.
He's doing that with just his fingers?! Is he trying to break the palace down?!
Okay! I am so not into this! I'll check you later!
Kami, I need a favor from you.
Is that his own strength?
Yeah. He hasn't taken a single energy steroid. Not yet, at least.
He just destroyed that pillar!
Damn! The creep's flooding the joint!
I came here for a banquet, not a drowning!
Oh, crap! Water drops!
Hit the deck! He's gonna do it!
Ahhhh...
Oh, crap! Water drops!
Hit the deck! He's gonna do it!
Ahhhh!
Shark arrows!
Who's going to hit the guards?
You monster!
My guards are innocent men.
How dare you shoot them down?
Leave them be!
You deranged preton!
King Neptune!
You can't do that, sir!
Your lives are my responsibility.
Pride is no!
Cinnamon fool!
Risking his life for lowly pawns.
Just more proof that you don't have what it takes to be gay!
King Neptune!
Damn you, Horty!
Why? They're chained and unarmed.
Damn, he's brutal.
Also, he's way stronger than Arlong ever was.
Huh?
One-sword-style bird dance!
Wait, boss, please!
Can't you just move out of the way?
That creep!
He used his own crewmate as a shield!
Hey, you two.
Go untie all of the soldiers.
Huh?
Our negotiation with the kingdom, it collapsed.
We gave them our word to give back all the hostages unharmed, and we couldn't keep that promise.
That's honest!
You're right.
I'm on it!
Alright, my foot's in the water!
I can feel my life draining away!
Help me, Nami!
Wait, where's Nami?
Look!
Huh?
She's gone?
It's not just her!
He's gone!
Yeah, I have to move out, too!
Oh, he's gone!
Oh, my foot's in the water!
I can feel my life draining away!
Help me, Nami!
Wait, where's Nami?
Look!
Huh?
Hunter, Kami has gone missing, too.
Oh, great. We're losing our friends left and right.
First priority is releasing these guys, though.
Just try to hang in there and keep at it, Brook.
Always riding my bones.
I recommend running now.
Oh, I need you to untie your other comrades, please.
I'm afraid I don't have the energy for it.
Untie the others quickly and take up your arms.
Don't let them do a damn thing.
Destroy Neptune's army and the Straw Hats.
Kill them all.
Special attack, Green Star, Rappel Siak.
Whoa, that shot turned into a giant flower.
Such exotic flora.
Breathe deep.
Damn bunch of fools.
Enjoy.
I'm dying here.
Come on, Zoro.
Let's move.
Listen up.
Do me a favor and help those two get out of here.
And what about you?
We're not gonna make it out of here.
Not if that guy's chasing us.
This is a revolution.
And you're in the way.
All right.
Well, that's a relief.
Doesn't look like anything's broken.
Sorry I put you through the ringer like that, partner.
You just rest here for a while and build your strength back up.
Hey, pal.
You wanna help me out with the coating?
Not necessary.
A man's best off sticking to his own trade.
Good point.
I'll leave you to it.
Well, look at that.
There you are.
Sunny.
Heya, Robin.
Huh?
This a friend of yours?
Yep.
You finish up all your business?
Not yet.
I've still got something big I need to check on.
And there it is.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Outsiders aren't supposed to go in there!
Thanks.
I'll keep that in mind.
Huh.
She's a weird one, huh?
Seriously?
No offense, but look who's talking.
Quite impressive.
You were the only one quick enough to dodge my arrows.
But then again, you've seen them before.
I have a lot of respect for Arlong,
but I've surpassed him.
Your skills are inconsequential now.
You're helpless here.
No human stands a chance against a fish man in the sea.
Ah.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
There's no deflecting my arrows in the water.
Three-sword style.
Tatsumaki!
Oh, not bad.
I can let loose.
I can't keep this up for much longer.
Just stay with me, Hachi.
You're gonna be okay.
You...
Ugh.
No, you need to get out of here.
Quit worrying about us.
We'll be fine.
Come on.
Focus on you first.
What's up with the angry mob?
Give us back the mermaids!
Yeah, we're nothing but objects to you humans!
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb, pirates!
The words got around town.
We know you did it!
We know you kidnapped all those poor mermaids from the beach in the south!
Where did you take them, huh?
You've got the wrong guys here.
Besides, what gives you the idea that we're the ones behind this?
I mean, I will admit it.
But it's so good to you all.
You're as bad.
You're not a guy, are you?
I'm not a guy, dude.
You're not a guy-
Everyone's behind this. I mean, I will admit...
I love mermaids so much I want to keep them all for myself!
Regardless, our crew didn't kidnap them.
You hear that? He just admitted that he wants them!
Will you jerks shut up? There's a dying man here!
I knew you pirates were guilty!
Get off our island!
Hey, this bottle is almost full! That's a waste of good booze!
Shut up, human!
Oh, hey! Sanji! Chopper!
Hey, Sanji! Get your nose under control!
Luffy! Is that... a blowfish?
Who is that human, gentlemen?
And is that... a raccoon!
It looks just like the picture I saw!
You know them, Luffy? Your friends?
Yeah. Those guys are my crew members.
Wow, interesting crew.
Look! Up there, the captain of the Straw Hat crew!
You're right, it is!
You gave the order to kidnap the mermaids, didn't you?
We can't let all of the people down there see me!
Hey! Shut your mouth! Hurry!
I'm gonna go check things out on the ground!
Huh?
He jumped off!
Hey, Hachi! What happened?
You... Leaf Straw Hat.
Did some jerk do this to you? Tell me who it was!
We tried, but he won't say for some reason!
You have to get off the island!
Ugh...
That's the only thing he'll say.
Hang on a second!
I heard that Straw Hat had taken over the Ryugu Palace!
It's a ploy!
He's out to kidnap more of us mermaids!
He left his men at the palace so he could go out marauding!
I know what he wants!
He's gonna kidnap Princess Shirahoshi, too!
Oh, don't be ridiculous!
That's absurd and you know it!
The princess is the size of an orca!
Plus, she's the god of the sea's only daughter, remember?
Some lowlife might dream of kidnapping her,
but nobody could pull it off!
Huh?
What's up with that blowfish?
No!
Aaxo!
Ah!
Augh!
Hey!
Oh, shit!
Okay, stop this!
Aaaaaaaaahhhhhhh!
Princess Shira Hochi!
I uh...
Well um...
You see...
Uh...
Good job! You found me!
She's huge!
Oh no!
Is she...
Oh!
The Mermaid Princess!
Hey, what's up?
Something going on behind me?
No, it's nothing!
No matter what you hear, please don't turn around!
Huh? Why? What's the big deal?
Don't do it!
I don't want you to die, Saji!
Ah jeez...
The pirates! They kidnapped the princess!
Oh no!
Luffy is captured by a group of stalwart fishermen
who are enraged by Shira Hochi's apparent kidnapping.
Suddenly, Van Der Decken appears,
forcing Luffy into combat despite his arms being tied.
If Luffy can escape to the sea forest,
he will be reunited with Saji,
but the lecherous shaft may not survive the sight of the Mermaid Princess.
On the next, One Piece,
keep Shira Hochi safe!
Deck it close behind!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!